/*---------------------------Questions for Difficult Level------------------------*/
/*-------------------------------------------------------------------------------*/
window.gameDifficultLevelQuestions = [
    {
        question: "100 + 201 / 3 - 67  = ?",
        answerArray: ["101", "201", "100", "301"],
        matchedValue: "100",
        correctAnswer: "100",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "1696 - 563 * (43 - 39) = ?",
        answerArray: ["-555", "-554", "-556", "-558"],
        matchedValue: "-556",
        correctAnswer: "-556",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "15 * 15 * 15 = ?",
        answerArray: ["3375", "225", "3345", "2250"],
        matchedValue: "3375",
        correctAnswer: "3375",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "121 / 11 / 11 = ?",
        answerArray: ["11", "0", "1", "111"],
        matchedValue: "1",
        correctAnswer: "1",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "123 + 321 + (444 - 888) = ?",
        answerArray: ["444", "0", "111", "222"],
        matchedValue: "0",
        correctAnswer: "0",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "789 - 453 = ?",
        answerArray: ["336", "452", "876", "123"],
        matchedValue: "336",
        correctAnswer: "336",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "76 * 12 = ?",
        answerArray: ["812", "312", "345", "912"],
        matchedValue: "912",
        correctAnswer: "912",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "786 / 3 * (1/3 + 5/3) = ?",
        answerArray: ["526", "131", "130", "524"],
        matchedValue: "524",
        correctAnswer: "524",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "675 + 125 - 125 = ?",
        answerArray: ["675", "0", "125", "1000"],
        matchedValue: "675",
        correctAnswer: "675",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "6 / 2 (1 + 2) = ?",
        answerArray: ["9", "1", "2", "6"],
        matchedValue: "9",
        correctAnswer: "9",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "79 - 13 - (-13) = ?",
        answerArray: ["63", "53", "43", "33"],
        matchedValue: "53",
        correctAnswer: "53",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "[(89 * 11) / 0.001]/100 = ?",
        answerArray: ["97.9", "979", "9790", "9.79"],
        matchedValue: "9790",
        correctAnswer: "9790",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "654 + 123 = ?",
        answerArray: ["777", "778", "888", "678"],
        matchedValue: "777",
        correctAnswer: "777",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "(354 - 145) + (575 - 784) = ?",
        answerArray: ["209", "0", "1", "-209"],
        matchedValue: "0",
        correctAnswer: "0",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "11 * 33 * 0.1 = ?",
        answerArray: ["36.3", "363", "3630", "3.63"],
        matchedValue: "36.3",
        correctAnswer: "36.3",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "810 / 9 * 9 = ?",
        answerArray: ["9", "10", "810", "100"],
        matchedValue: "810",
        correctAnswer: "810",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "[(11 + 9)(11 - 9)] * (9999/3333)  = ?",
        answerArray: ["110", "100", "300", "120"],
        matchedValue: "120",
        correctAnswer: "120",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "785 - 15 * 15 = ?",
        answerArray: ["500", "560", "520", "510"],
        matchedValue: "560",
        correctAnswer: "560",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "135 * 9 = ?",
        answerArray: ["1335", "1115", "1215", "1445"],
        matchedValue: "1215",
        correctAnswer: "1215",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "195 / 5 * 0.01 = ?",
        answerArray: ["39", "0.039", "0.39", "390"],
        matchedValue: "0.39",
        correctAnswer: "0.39",
        isVisited: 0
    }
];

